Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
To submerge a town for dam construction,
they demolish the buildings first.
But here, they flooded it as it is.
What do you mean?
They sank the entire village undamaged.
Last fall,
a TV crew came with a few divers,
wanting to film Korea's Atlantis,
as they called it.
The villagers protested
and even broke their equipment.
The administrator in charge
almost lost his job.
Why?
Don't you know what people call it?
The man-eating lake.
They don't call it haunted for nothing.
What? You think it's funny?
No, sir.
Don't think about going in there.
Sorry?
I know that you're a diver.
-You're itching to see what's in there.
-I'm not.
Don't take me for a fool.
This lake gives me the creeps.
You might think it's bullshit,
but stay clear of it.
Because it's not just any old lake.
Green light, green light, red light!
Hey, you're not supposed to move!
You moved!
I saw you move.
SERYUNG VILLAGE
Ernie!
Where did you go?
Quit playing around!
Ernie!
Where are you?
Why do you keep doing this?
Where are you going?
For God's sake!
I'm telling you.
If we stay here, we'll all die!
Stop this nonsense.
Bloody rain will fall!
Enough of this!
Get a hold of yourself!
Father, I saw it.
The water reeks of blood.
We've got to fill in the well.
How can you not see it?
Look over there. Right there!
You see? Right there.
That water is swallowing people.
Father, look-- No!
Sucking them up and swallowing them!
It'll swallow us all!
Patrol two rescued a young boy
near Seryung Dam.
Returning to the precinct.
The situation appears urgent.
Send further assistance.
Repeat, urgent. Send backup.
What happened to Dad?
Mr. Choi, Can you hear me?
Mr. Choi Hyun-su!
PARAMEDICS
YEAR 2004
Let's get the farewell party started.
-Is everyone ready?
-Ready!
Here we go!
Let's go!
TWO WEEKS BEFORE THE INCIDENT
-Let's go!
-Here we go!
Mom, the playground here is huge!
Unbelievable.
You haven't left yet?
What are you thinking?
You're already late!
I told you. I didn't hear it ring.
Didn't I tell you that
the guy next door is expecting you?
A farewell party?
Are we moving to another country?
Get moving already.
We don't have much time to pack.
-Hey!
-Is it Dad?
Quiet! Don't jump!
Dad!
Hey, son.
This apartment is ours! Yes!
It's got two bathrooms,
and the rooms are huge.
They even have a library in the complex.
Mom said when I go to middle school,
we'll move here. Is that for real?
It is, right?
Hurry back, okay?
Seriously? You bought an apartment?
I know.
-How big is it?
-It's 32 pyeong.
Quit messing around!
No joke.
That's awesome, man.
"Awesome"? You don't know the half of it.
We took out a bank loan,
but I can barely afford the interest.
How am I going to pay for it?
Not with my security guard paycheck.
Then what are you going to do?
What can I do?
There's a staff house freeing up.
So we'll rent out the apartment
and move there.
Damn, my wife won't stop calling.
I'm off.
Are you sure you can drive?
Take a nap first!
Take care!
The number you're calling
is unavailable at the moment.
Please leave a message after the tone.
This is Security Officer Ahn.
I'm waiting for you at the house.
Please let me know if you're still coming.
Where is this guy?
I'm almost there, about 30 minutes out.
How many times should I tell you?
Don't just rush in and out.
Make sure you look carefully.
Check the electricity
and gas meters first.
Also, see if there's room
for a washing machine.
And there's an oil boiler?
You know,
we need to be clear on the costs.
-Eun-ju, I see some cops up ahead.
-Hyun-su!
I'm serious. I have to go.
-Bye.
-Hello?
Hello? Hyun-su?
What is the matter with him?
DR. OH YOUNG-JE
Hello, it's me.
Where is Ha-young?
Where is she?
The court ruling?
That means nothing to me.
Ten years as husband and wife
will not be cut off
by a mere court ruling.
Come on. Let's go.
I give her one week.
Tell Ha-young.
If she doesn't come back until then,
she should prepare herself.
She'll know very well what that means.
You know how I am.
I will…
never give her up.
What the--
That punk is starting to piss me off!
Dad, I feel like I'm suffocating.
Ha-young!
I can't take it anymore.
If things stay this way,
both Se-ryung and I will die…
SERYUNG VILLAGE
WELCOME
Dad, I feel like I'm suffocating.
Ha-young!
I can't take it anymore.
If things stay this way,
both Se-ryung and I will die in his hands.
Hell would feel like heaven without him.
You don't know him, Dad.
He is the devil himself.
Good evening, Dr. Oh.
Get up.
I told you not to touch Mom's things.
You keep disobeying your daddy.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again. I'm sorry.
I want to ask you something.
Will you answer me honestly?
Yes.
Se-ryung.
You still talk to your mom, don't you?
Just like your mother.
Keeping your mouth shut.
Go stand in front of the closet.
It's her, isn't it?
Hey, Ha-young. It's me.
It's okay. You can talk.
I want to apologize to you.
Don't you miss Se-ryung?
Ha-young?
Ha-young.
Answer me, damn it!
You probably think
I wouldn't be able to find you.
If I track this phone,
I'll find you right away.
Are you not scared of me
because you can't see me?
You keep forgetting who I am.
You don't remember? Try harder.
After all I've done for you…
Se-ryung!
Oh, Se-ryung!
Go on!
Hide away.
Daddy will find you.
Okay?
Se-ryung!
This is Ahn again.
Something's come up,
so I have to step out.
You can take a look around first.
I'll text you the door pass code.
Mr. Ahn! It's me, Se-ryung.
Open the door, please!
Mr. Ahn! Are you home?
Please, open the door.
Mr. Ahn! Please.
Do you know where Se-ryung might go?
Where?
Did I pass the exit?
Se-ryung!
There's my good girl.
But you know,
I'll make you pay for this!
You hear me?
BLOCKED NUMBER
I need to see Seo-won.
I'm not going!
Seo-won.
He's the one who has refused
to see me until now.
He's the one
that abandoned me.
RAMPAGE KILLER CHOI HYUN-SU
That magazine is driving me crazy.
People scorn us
for being tied to a murderer.
These magazines were even sent
to his school and the neighbors.
-Just send him away.
-But where to?
Wherever, I don't care!
Just like his father,
he'll do something terrible.
What about this apartment?
It belongs to Seo-won.
I don't care! Send him away!
RAMPAGE KILLER CHOI HYUN-SU
Seo-won!
They're gone.
I got back from my school trip,
and they even changed their phone numbers.
You were the only one I could think of.
He's not coming.
I guess he needs more time.
These days, he's helping out on the boat
and also gives diving instructions.
Now, he's a better diver than I am.
What about school?
How could he go back to school
after all that's happened?
"Rampage killer Choi Hyun-su.
After mercilessly murdering
a 12-year-old girl
and drowning half of the villagers
by opening the dam gate,
he refused to defend himself.
'Execute me.'
Even the moment he was sentenced to death,
Choi Hyun-su remained emotionless.
His wife, Kang Eun-ju,
was found near Seryung Lake
two days after the incident, drowned.
His son, who is said to be
the only survivor of the family,
will live with his relatives."
Give me that.
Is that why you transferred here?
You bastard!
-You murderer! How dare you--
-Get up.
Let's check out some other schools.
Where?
I'm done with all of this.
I'm sick and tired of running away.
Come out, you bastard.
Don't go behind my back.
Come out and say it to my face!
If you want revenge,
do it to the one in jail!
They'll execute me soon.
Hyun-su.
Every morning, my heart pounds,
wondering if today will be the day.
I need to see Seo-won.
CORRECTIONAL CENTER
ADVANCED CORRECTIONAL SERVICES
FOR A BETTER FUTURE
I'm here to visit someone.
He doesn't want to meet his son.
Why not?
He'll only meet with the guardian.
Searching for a missing child.
Oh Se-ryung, a 12-year-old girl.
A coin-sized birthmark
on the left side of the back of the neck.
If you see a girl
who fits this description…
-Se-ryung!
-Se-ryung, where are you?
Excuse me. Sir?
Your car's fixed.
You're lucky it was just a deer.
If it was a boar or something else,
you'd be gone already.
Shake it off and move on.
Dad.
Where have you been?
I couldn't reach you,
and you ignored all my texts.
Where is your jacket?
Back to drinking again?
It drives me crazy when I can't reach you!
-Where are you going?
-I'm going to wash up.
Hey, I saved up your puny salary
to get us an apartment,
and that still isn't enough?
You didn't stop by the house.
Are you doing this to piss me off?
You can't even do that one thing for me?
I had to call them to get it sorted out!
What?
I said, I had to call them!
You made a fuss over something
that could be…
handled by just one phone call?
Why do I have to take care of everything
in this goddamn house?
It was a five-hour drive back and forth!
Did you just hit me?
Of course, this runs in your blood.
You're just like your father!
Go on! Hit me!
Do it! Hit me! Go ahead and hit me!
Hit me!
Hit me! You crazy asshole!
Hit me! Do it!
You crazy bastard, hit me!
Wow, a dam.
You really didn't see anything?
A 12-year-old girl went missing.
Did Dr. Oh put you up to this?
To interrogate me?
Don't take offense.
Plus, there was that incident last time.
A 12-year-old girl was crying alone
in the woods.
In her pajamas.
-Her body was covered in bruises.
-I know, but--
But the girl's father
called me a sex offender
and got me locked up all day.
I know there are hard feelings
between you and Dr. Oh,
but you stand to gain nothing
by crossing him.
Understood?
What? What is it?
I'm Choi Hyun-su.
Oh, the new security supervisor!
What brings you
to our shabby little village?
It's a little noisy, isn't it?
You've come at the worst time.
A few days ago, a young girl disappeared.
What?
Her mother must've taken her.
Where can she have gone?
Drink up, and we'll go
have a look at the dam.
This dam was built
by blocking the river in the middle,
so the water flow is heavy.
We keep the gates open
except during drought.
Otherwise, the water fills up right away.
-Here.
-Thank you.
MISSING CHILD
OH SE-RYUNG, FEMALE, AGE 12
The girl who disappeared.
You mean, Se-ryung?
Do you know her?
Her dad's got a notorious reputation.
He's a successful dentist
and has a big clinic in the city.
He owns half of the land here,
so it's hard not to know him.
Everyone calls him Dr. Oh.
Of course, whatever you say.
You're the boss.
Got it.
So he got that permit after all?
Once Dr. Oh sets his mind to something,
he's unstoppable.
Sir, they can search the lake
starting tomorrow.
Seo-won!
Get back in here.
We have to unpack!
MISSING CHILD
OH SE-RYUNG, FEMALE, AGE 12
You punks! Don't go in there!
Don't disturb the old lake.
You'll kill the entire village!
-Move back.
-Everyone will die!
Step back, or I'll arrest you
for obstructing the police!
Who cares about that
when doom could befall our village?
Get out right now, you idiots!
What happened?
What happened to Se-ryung?
Dr. Oh, your father-in-law is here.
My gosh, sir!
You don't need to be out here.
-Young-je! Se-ryung is okay, right?
-Ma'am!
Don't worry.
We're searching the lake just in case.
We'll tell you if we find something,
so go home for now.
-Don't worry.
-Is everything all right?
It's nothing to worry about,
so just go home.
-Take them home.
-Yes, sir.
What's all the fuss about?
They say a child fell.
Why would a child go in there?
She must have been possessed.
What did I say?
I told you something would happen!
-We should've filled it a long time ago.
-I know.
What did I say?
I told you something would happen!
We should've filled it.
He got all drunk and lost his footing.
What are you talking about?
Who would fall into a well by accident?
He was possessed by the well.
We found the body!
Se-ryung! Get up!
Go home at once!
Chief.
We got something.
There's a car entering the upstream area.
Right there, at 11:02 p.m.
Keep going.
There's another one driving down.
It looks like the same car.
That is suspicious.
That road leads to the cliff.
No one ever drives on that road at night.
What do you make of it?
-It looks like a small sedan.
-Send it over for analysis.
Yes, sir.
Dr. Oh, will you come with me
to the precinct?
Was it an accident or not?
MISSING CHILD
OH SE-RYUNG, FEMALE, AGE 12
Shut up!
Shut your mouth!
Die!
Seo-won--
Seo-won?
Seo-won!
-Hyun-su.
-Seo-won.
Hyun-su!
-Calling upon the dead
-Come out and cleanse your soul
It's a ritual to save the soul.
My dad used to recover bodies
from the water,
so I've seen this a lot since I was young.
It looks like there was a car accident.
She suffered a brain hemorrhage.
Her neck and skull were broken.
But the direct cause of death
was something else.
Asphyxia caused
by forced airway obstruction.
The suspect suffocated her to death
by covering her mouth,
then dumped the body in the lake.
There are no signs of sexual assault.
Where did you learn that?
My mom was like this for a while
after my dad died in a diving accident.
Let go.
I've never even seen that girl.
Liar.
I saw you.
She's dead!
Come with me.
You're my friend, aren't you?
Let him go! Don't touch him!
Dad!
-Don't do this!
-Mr. Kim, ring the emergency siren.
Dad--
-Seo-won!
-Dad!
Dad.
I saw the dead girl.
The day the police came,
I went to the lake with some other kids.
We had just gotten there,
and she came out of the water.
Her face looked so scary and strange.
It made me feel sick,
but some lady
covered my eyes.
Stay still and don't look.
If you look into the eyes of the dead,
you'll never get away from them.
Every night, she comes and finds me.
I want to tell her
that she can't come here,
but I can't speak.
She says if she hadn't died,
we would've been classmates.
Because her seat was next to mine.
Dad.
That girl is dead, right?
Green light, green light, red light!
We found signs of repetitive abuse
on the child's body.
Can you explain this?
Are you suggesting…
that I strangled my daughter
and threw her in the lake?
I heard you're in the middle of a divorce.
Habitual physical and verbal abuse.
I heard you rule with an iron fist.
Dr. Oh.
Is your wife's name Moon Ha-young?
Yes.
Are you sure?
All right.
They just found your wife's body in Suwon.
It looks like a suicide.
She hanged herself.
Dr. Oh?
Bitch.
Apparently, Ha-young is dead.
What did you say?
She hanged herself.
She left everything and ran away,
only to kill herself?
You killed them.
Both Ha-young and Se-ryung.
Do you think
this will bring Se-ryung back?
Whoever it is, I'll find the bastard
that killed her and make him pay!
Continue.
Hit the gong. Hit it!
Shut up!
I said shut up!
Die! Just die!
He moved here recently.
I've seen him do that many times.
The first time must have been
last Friday.
He was walking
with his shoes in his hands.
I thought it was weird, so I followed him.
He threw the shoes in the lake
and started balling his eyes out.
He didn't even see me standing there,
as if he was possessed by something.
This is for diving,
not fishing.
It's fluorescent,
so it's probably for night diving.
When you're diving at night,
you can barely see anything as it's dark.
So if you mark the intervals like this,
you can check the depth
and easily find your way out.
Ahn Seung-hwan, 32 years old.
He's been working as a dam security guard
since last November.
No prior convictions.
He used to be in the SSU,
the Ship Salvage Unit.
From now on, use this phone to contact me.
It's a burner phone, so it's untraceable.
-Mom.
-Too small.
Look at his shoes.
The soles are all worn down.
Hey!
I bought them one size bigger.
I'll return them tomorrow.
He says they're not small.
We can buy three pairs
with the money you spent on these.
Don't be so stingy with our son!
He's going to middle school soon.
We must save up for his college.
-I'll return them.
-I said, no!
-Dad, I don't need these.
-You stay quiet.
What about the apartment?
We have to pay back the loan!
Enough with the apartment!
All of this is because of
that damn apartment!
Hey! Stop!
Don't do it!
You worthless bastard!
Before there was 911,
there were people whose job was to fish
drowned bodies out of the water.
They were called alligators.
Back then, kids learned to dive at age 12.
I asked you why this was there.
And I'm telling you that I'm an alligator.
That's why I was there that night,
around the time of Se-ryung's death.
Who is your scapegoat this time?
You don't remember?
Accusing me of being a sex offender?
That's funny?
Let me tell you something really funny.
That night,
Se-ryung came by.
Mr. Ahn!
Are you sleeping?
Mr. Ahn, are you home?
She had dried blood on her face.
-She called me again and again.
-Mr. Ahn?
I just hid behind the door.
Mr. Ahn! Open the door, please!
You know why?
I didn't want to be called
a sex offender again.
How about that? Is that funny?
If I let her in that night,
Se-ryung would still be alive,
you bastard!
This is Oh Young-je.
Get me the plate numbers of all the cars
that passed through the tollgate
on the night of the 29th.
Chief.
There's a car entering the upstream area.
At 11:02 p.m.
There's another one driving down
25 minutes later.
It looks like the same car.
Dad…
Hyun-su…
Stop there!
Hyun-su.
Shut up!
Die!
Die! Just die!
We found the body!
Over here. Come on!
Pull him up!
Dr. Oh?
Yes, the dead girl's father.
SERYUNG IC TRAFFIC RECORD
He asked me when you moved here.
Why?
He said he's seen you somewhere.
See you later!
MISSING CHILD
OH SE-RYUNG, FEMALE, AGE 12
You can stop coming.
Okay?
What do you need it for?
Mr. Ahn!
Mr. Ahn, are you in there?
It's Seo-won. Please open the door!
Mr. Ahn, is something wrong with my dad?
Your dad is having a dream.
A bad dream.
Just like my dreams about that girl?
I don't go out when she calls me,
but Dad follows, doesn't he?
Hyun-su…
Dad!
Dad.
Are you okay?
Luckily, no bones were broken.
Hence, only a temporary cast.
Why aren't you
asking questions?
You know
what I've been doing every night.
My father…
was a disabled soldier.
He lost an arm in the Vietnam War.
People called him
"Crazy Dog."
Sergeant Crazy Dog Choi.
Mom's dead!
There was an old well
in the village where I lived.
A dark and deep well.
You couldn't see the bottom.
I took my dad's army boots
and went to the well.
They said if shoes fell into the well,
the owner of the shoes would die.
Die, you asshole!
Then, I heard my dad's voice from inside.
Hyun-su.
"Hyun-su."
I thought the well was talking to me.
The villagers said the well was haunted.
They said it was alive.
Shut up and die!
I threw in the other shoe.
Then I heard my dad's voice again.
Hyun-su.
"Hyun-su."
Help me.
"Help me."
Hyun-su.
I covered my ears and ran away.
I thought I was dreaming.
My dad's eyes
were staring at me.
My dad, whom I hated so much.
But we are exactly the same.
The way we look
and the way we behave.
Even the way we drink--
I'm just like my father.
But Seo-won can be different.
He should never be like me.
What's going on with you?
I've got a night shift.
You're on sick leave!
Mom.
Get out for a second.
Let's go, Seo-won.
Hyun-su.
The police came by this morning.
That night I asked you
to check out the house--
were you here?
You weren't, right?
Okay, then.
Dr. Oh, I found it.
He brought in his car
the day after the accident.
He paid cash.
The police had already come and left.
But Dr. Oh,
they said Choi Hyun-su called.
To turn himself in.
Did you know about this?
Go away!
Now!
Get away from here!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What's your son's height?
Around 150 centimeters?
Or 160 centimeters?
I heard the water will fill up right away
if you close the dam gate.
How long can he stay alive?
Seo-won!
Spare him.
Sir, please! I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Dr. Oh!
My boy is innocent! Dr. Oh!
Kill me! I said, kill me!
You bastard!
I killed her, so just kill me!
Leave my son out of this!
You bastard!
Help!
Anyone there?
Help me!
Why did you do it?
You didn't have to kill her.
Why did you kill her?
Why?
The fog was thick.
I had been drinking,
so I got lost.
All of a sudden, there she was.
I couldn't believe that…
I had killed someone.
Then her cell phone rang.
I thought she was dead,
but she opened her eyes
and whispered in my ear.
I had never heard anything
more petrifying.
I heard it more than a hundred times.
I still hear it in my dreams
and even when I'm awake.
What did she say?
I didn't want to kill her.
I just wanted to stop the ringing.
What did she say?
Daddy.
I'm sorry.
Dad!
IN CASE OF MALFUNCTION, OPERATE MANUALLY
The engine room.
ENGINE ROOM
Seo-won?
Seo-won needs help!
-He's trapped!
-Hyun-su?
I need to open the gate! Now!
-Can you hear me?
-He'll die!
Seo-won! Seo-won is trapped!
Wait! You'll kill everyone!
If you open the gate, everyone will die!
Hello?
You'll kill everyone to save your son?
No!
Help!
Dad!
Seo-won!
Se-ryung!
I'm sorry, Se-ryung.
I'm so sorry, Se-ryung.
Dad!
Help me!
Just this once!
Please!
Help me!
Dad!
You've never done anything for me!
Just this once!
Please!
Seo-won!
Are you okay?
I…
committed an unforgivable sin.
I killed people,
and I can only pay back with my life.
Seo-won.
Oh Young-je came to visit.
Se-ryung's father.
He wants me to suffer as much as he did.
He wants me to see you die in front of me.
Just like that day seven years ago.
Why did you do it?
Why did you save me?
Because of me,
dozens of people died.
Why? Just so I could live like this?
Look at me.
Look at me!
Why did you save me?
Why?
Because…
I'm your father.
I came to see you every month.
For three years,
I came here every month!
Mr. Ahn.
Yes?
Why didn't you leave me?
For seven years. We don't share
a single drop of blood.
Why?
I was afraid you'd die
if I ignored you
like I ignored Se-ryung that night.
Dad wanted me to thank you
on his behalf
for everything you've done.
And I feel the same way.
You're really something.
You're still alive.
I thought you would've
killed yourself by now.
RAMPAGE KILLER CHOI HYUN-SU
Still, I'm glad you're not happy.
I wanted your dad
to see you hang yourself.
Hang in there.
We're almost there.
Inside Seryung Lake.
That's where you will die.
Seo-won.
Your father's dead.
Seo-won!
Breaking news. This morning,
death row inmate Choi Hyun-su
hanged himself in his prison cell.
He was rushed to the hospital but died.
Choi was sentenced to death
after killing a 12-year-old girl
and drowning half of the residents
in the village.
Choi Hyun-su--
what a shameless coward.
Whether you're alive or dead,
it doesn't matter.
It's still vivid.
The first time I saw Ha-young,
I felt this sense of thirst
for the first time.
Like I never felt before.
She was a beautiful, good woman.
Except that
she had no love for me.
But that wasn't a problem.
Because…
she would love me eventually.
I thought we were almost there.
A little more effort.
Just a little more.
Then both Ha-young…
and Se-ryung…
Your dad ruined everything.
Choi Hyun-su.
Do you think you can change anything?
It only ends when I end it!
Green light, green light, red light!
Seo-won!
Shall we get going?
This was among Dad's belongings.
MISSING CHILD
OH SE-RYUNG, FEMALE, AGE 12
He apologized
to Se-ryung
and to everyone else.